[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The idea about Barbie came to her creator Ruth Handler, when she saw an adult looking doll called this.", "correct_answer": "Lilli", "incorrect_answers": ["Henrieta", "Margaretta", "Gretta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "President Kennedy had a secretary named Lincoln and Lincoln had a secretary named Kennedy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This term, related to the origin of the Universe, was proposed by George Lemaitre, a Belgian Roman Catholic priest and astronomer.", "correct_answer": "The Big Bang", "incorrect_answers": ["The Milky Way", "The Boom", "Y-Chromosome"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these French actresses stars in the Public Enemies movie from 2009 as criminal John Dillingers love interest?", "correct_answer": "Marion Cotillard", "incorrect_answers": ["Ludivine Sagnier", "Hafsia Herzi", "Emmanuelle Seigner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dodos other name was The Robert Don.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not true about the egg yolk?", "correct_answer": "It contains 75% of the protein of the egg.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is placed in a yolk sac.", "Its usual color varies from pale yellow to deep orange.", "It contains almost 100% of total amount of fat and cholesterol in the egg."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular gun was invented by General John  T. Thompson?", "correct_answer": "tommy gun", "incorrect_answers": ["the JT assault rifle", "johnny gun", "sten gun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rangipo Desert in the central part of New Zealands North Island, does not have its barren and lifeless appearance because of the lack of rain, but rather, due to which of these?", "correct_answer": "Soil structure", "incorrect_answers": ["Intense use of pesticides", "Constant powerful winds", "Frequent destructive storms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is found in plant cells, but not in animal cells?", "correct_answer": "Chloroplast", "incorrect_answers": ["Mitochondria", "Cytoplasm", "Ribosomes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country owns the .ie domain name?", "correct_answer": "Ireland", "incorrect_answers": ["Northern Ireland (Ulster)", "Israel", "Iceland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The beagle was developed mainly for tracking what animal?", "correct_answer": "rabbits", "incorrect_answers": ["squirrels", "raccoons", "coyotes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most distant object you can see unaided under the best possible conditions?", "correct_answer": "Triangulum Galaxy(M33)", "incorrect_answers": ["Andromeda Galaxy(M31)", "The Large Magellanic Cloud", "The Whirlpool Galaxy(M51)"]}]